Guide to the Steele Ranch Records, 1855-1973
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES A. CORRESPONDENCE: 1855-1973
  - Correspondence, 1950-1955 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - 48. 1955, April 14.Bronxville, N.Y. Kathy to C.[B.]S., W.[F.S.] and W.[W.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 49. 1955, May 23.San Mateo, Ca. San Mateo County Historical Assc. (F.M.S.) to Mr. & Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 50. 1955, May 31.San Carlos, Ca. Emma H. Kalenborn to [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 51. 1955, May 31.San Mateo, Ca. San Mateo County Historical Assc. (F.M.S.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 52. 1955, June 17.San Jose, Ca. Dept. of Agric. - County of Santa Clara (T.J.M.) to Mrs. W.[F.]S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 53. 1955, June 28.Washington, D.C. U.S. Coast Guard (A.E.C.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 54. 1955, July 5.Santa Cruz. Ca. Baikie and Alcantara (B.B.) to Mr. & Mrs. W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 55. 1955, July 13.Washington, D.C. U.S. Coast Guard (A.E.C.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 56. 1955, Oct. 26.[Santa Cruz, Ca.]. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co., Inc. (E.J.A.*) to [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 57. 1955, Dec. 12.San Luis Obispo, Ca. Estelle B. Hunter to [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 58. 1955, Dec. 13.S.F., Ca. Calif. Historical Society (G.C.W.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 59. 1955, Dec. 17.N.P. H_____(?) Sciaroni to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 60. 1955, Dec. 19.Modesto, Ca. John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. (E.B.**) to W.F.S., T.L.S.
  - Sympathy Cards & Letters, [1956]. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Sympathy Cards & Letters, [1956]. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - 1. 1956, Jan. 3.San Luis Obispo, Ca. San Luis Obispo County Historical Society (G.R.N.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 2. 1956, Jan. 22.S.F., Ca. Calif. Historical Society (G.C.W.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 3. 1956, Jan. 26.San Carlos, Ca. H[ank] Sciaroni to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 4. 1956, Jan. 29.Berkeley, Ca. Unknown to [C.B.S.]. frag., T.L.
    - 5. 1956, Jan. 30.Sacramento, Ca. May Steele to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 6. 1956, Jan. 31.N.P. [Cardy] (?) to [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 7. 1956, Feb. 2.S.F., Ca. Calif. Historical Society (G.C.W.) to Mrs. W.F.S. [C.B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1956, Feb. 11.N.P. Doris to [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 9. 1956, Feb. 12.Clinton, N.Y. Alan Brown to Mr. & Mrs. [W.F.]S. re: passage from a book containing an account of an excursion made in the late 1800's in the Año Nuevo area., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1956, Feb. 16.N.P. Unidentified [Hank Sciaroni] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 11. 1956, Feb. 17.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Historical Society (J.E.C.) to W.[F.]S. & C.[B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 12. 1956, Mar. 5.Clinton, N.Y. Alan Brown to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 13. 1956, Mar. 18.San Carlos, Ca. Emma H. Kalenborn to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 14. 1956, April 16.Hamilton College. Alan Brown to [C.B.]S. re: interpretation of place names in the Año Nuevo area., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1956, April 18.S.F., Ca. Calif. Historical Society (G.C.W.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 16. 1956, May 12.Stanford, Ca. Kenneth B. O'Brien, Jr. to Mrs. W.C.S. [W.F.S.]., T.L.
    - 17. 1956, May 23.S.F., Ca. Goldstein, Barceloux and Goldstein (B.J.G.) to C.B.S. re: irrigation pipe line., T.L.S.
    - 18. 1956, May 23.Monterey, Ca. E.H. F[itch] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 19. 1956, June 4.S.F., Ca. Goldstein Barceloux & Goldstein (B.J.G.) to Mr. & Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 20. 1956, June 5.Reseda, Ca. Harriet H. Bern to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 21. 1956, June 5.S.F., Ca. Goldstein, Barceloux & Goldstein (B.J.G.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 22. 1956, June 26.N.P. Unknown to C.B.S., A.L.S.
    - 23. 1956, June 29.S.F., Ca. Harold H. Alvarez, D.D.S. to W.[F.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 24. 1956, July 21.Oak Knoll Hospital. Louise to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 25. 1956, July 29.C.E. Fehliman to Mrs. W.F.S. & W.[W.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1956, July 30.N.P. Melvin _____(?) to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1956, July 30.Houston, Texas. Margaret to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 28. 1956, July 30.Houston, Texas. Mother to [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 29. 1956, July 30.S.F., Ca. Carl L. Hoag, M.D. to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 30. 1956, July 31.Davenport, Ca. Louise [Hauselt] to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 31. 1956, July 31.Pescadero, Ca. Margues & Neel Reetzel(?) to Mrs. Steele., A.L.S.
    - 32. 1956, July 31.Santa Cruz, Ca. Loyd & Marie Miller to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 33. 1956, July 31.Monterey, Ca. E.H. F[itch] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 34. 1956, July 31.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Historical Society (M.S.D.) to Mrs. [C.B.]S. & family., A.L.S.
    - 35. 1956, Aug. 1.Houston, Texas. Stella [Tussell] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 36. 1956, Aug. 1.Lake Tahoe, Ca. May E. Steele to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 37. 1956, Aug. 1.N.P. Jeannette Rowland to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 38. 1956, Aug. 2.N.P. Kathy, Karen, Nathan [Hamilton] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 39. 1956, Aug. 3.Soquel, Ca. Lou & Mary Farnsworth to C.[B.S.] & W.[W.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 40. 1956, Aug. 3.N.P. Audrey B. _____(?) to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 41. 1956, Aug. 3.S.F., Ca. June Borina to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 42. 1956, Aug. 5.N.P. Hank Sciaroni to C.[B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 43. 1956, Aug. 6.Santa Cruz, Ca. Wessendorf Mortuary, Inc. (K.D.F.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 44. 1956, Aug. 8.Santa Cruz, Ca. Jeannette Rowland to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 45. 1956, Aug. 10.N.P. Richard Alvarez to C.[B.S.]., A.N.S.
    - 46. 1956, Aug. 11.N.P. Mildred Carmean to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 47. 1956, Aug. 13.S.F., Ca. Calif. Academy of Sciences (L.G.H.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 48. 1956, Aug. 14.Santa Cruz, Ca. Robert Burton to Mrs. W.[F.]S., A.L.S.
    - 49. 1956, Aug. 15.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co., Inc. (S.L.T.) to Member., T.L.
    - 50. 1956, Aug. 15.N.P. R.S. Miller to N.Y. Life Insur. Co., T.L.
    - 51. 1956, Aug. 15.N.P. Catherine Wolters Morris to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 52. 1956, Aug. 16.N.P. Tanner Wilson to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 53. 1956, Aug. 18.S.F., Ca. Louise to [C.B.S.] Kate., T.L.S.
    - 54. 1956, Aug. 19.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co., Inc. (E.J.A.*) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 55. 1956, Aug. 24.N.P. Carolyn to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 56. 1956, Aug. 27.Santa Cruz, Ca. Betty & Mike to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 57. 1956, Aug. 30.San Jose, Ca. Dept. of Agric. - Santa Clara County. (T.J.M.) to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 58. 1956, Sept. 5.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co., Inc. (E.J.A.*) to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 59. 1956, Sept. 5.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy Huggins(?) to C.[B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 60. 1956, Sept. 11.N.P. Doris Sciaroni to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 61. 1956, Sept. 17.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Historical Society (M.[S.]D.) to Mrs. W.F.S., A.L.S.
    - 62. 1956, Sept. 27.N.P. Unknown to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 63. 1956, Sept. 28.Nogales Son. Mex. Mr. & Mrs. Lawrence Apodoca & Son to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 64. 1956, Sept. 28.S.F., Ca. Calif. Society of the Sons of the American Revolution to Compatriot., T.L.
    - 65. 1956, Oct. Tuesday.N.P. Doris Sciaroni to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 66. [1956, Oct.].Watsonville, Ca. Sons of the American Revolution (G.W.R.) to Compatriot., T.L.S.
    - 67. 1956, Oct. 7.N.P. Unidentified to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 68. 1956, Oct. 16.Washington, D.C. National Geographic Society (T.W.M.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 69. 1956, Oct. 20.Carmel, Ca. Mary Vickrey to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 70. 1956, Nov. 16.N.P. Carolyn to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 71. 1956, Nov. 23.N.P. H[ank] [Sciaroni] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 72. 1956, Nov. 27.S.F., Ca. Firemans Fund Insur. Group to Our Insureds., T.L.S.
    - 73. 1956, Dec. 2.Monterey, Ca. E.N.F[itch] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 74. 1956, Dec. 6.Watsonville, Ca. George W. Reed to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 75. 1956, Dec. 6.S.F., Ca. Calif. Society of the Sons of the American Revolution (H.L.M.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 76. 1956, Dec. 7.N.P. F.W. Doyle to I.W. Hellman., T.L.S.
    - 77. 1956, Dec. 14.S.F., Ca. Wells Fargo Bank (I.W.H.) to Mrs. W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 78. 1956, Dec. 17.S.F., Ca. Firemans Fund Insur. Group (H.H.H.) to Andersen & Andersen., T.L.S.
    - 79. 1956, Dec. 28.N.P. H[ank] Sciaroni to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 80. 1856, Dec. 29.Monterey, Ca. V.M. Dabney to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - 1. 1957, Jan. 10.N.P. Ella N. Fitch to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 2. 1957, Jan. 24.San Mateo, Ca. J. A. Kellam to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 3. 1957, Feb. 15.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co., Inc. (S.L.T.) to Member., T.L.
    - 4. 1957, Feb. 15.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz, Land & Cattle Co., Inc. (E.J.A.*) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1957, Feb. 19.Santa Cruz, Ca. Odd Fellows Cemetery - Crematory - Mausoleum (E.B.B.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1957, Mar. 5.Santa Cruz, Ca. Harris Bros. (E.H.H.) to Mrs. W.[F.]S., T.L.
    - 7. 1957, Mar. 6.Stockton, Ca. Warmke & Woodward (L.E.W.) to Frank J. Murphy., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1957, Mar. 13.N.P. H[ank] Sciaroni to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 9. 1957, Mar. 14.N.P. R.H. Sciaroni to Carolyn Baldwin., T.L.
    - 10. 1957, Mar. 26.Monterey, Ca. E[lla] N. F[itch] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 11. 1957, April 4.Half Moon Bay, Ca. U.S. Dept. of Agric. (A.K.) to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 12. 1957, April 29.Watsonville, Ca. John L. McCarthy, attorney, to Elmer J. Abbott., T.L.S.
    - 13. 1957, April 30.Santa Cruz, Ca. Baikie & Alcantarra (R.D.B.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1957, May.Houston, Texas. Daughters of the Republic of Texas (M.A.) to Chapter Member., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1957, May 1.Davenport, Ca. W.W.S. to J. Frank Murphy., T.L.S.
    - 16. 1957, May 5.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co., Inc. (E.J.A.*) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 17. 1957, May 7.Santa Cruz, Ca. Baikie & Alcantara (R.D.B.) to Mrs. W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 18. 1957, May 7.Monterey, Ca. E.N. F[itch] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 19. 1957, May 8.Los Angeles, Ca. Richfield Oil Corp. (H.R.E.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 20. 1957, June 20.Monterey, Ca. E[lla] N. F[itch] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 21. 1957, June 27.Santa Cruz, Ca. Margaret M. Oliver to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 22. 1957, June 28.Watsonville, Ca. Pajaro Valley Bank (O.B.L.) to Stockholder, T.L.S.
    - 23. 1957, July 9.Los Angeles Ca. Richfield Oil Corp. (H.R.E.) to W.W.S., T.L.S.
    - 24. 1957, July 17.Los Angeles, Ca. Richfield Oil Corp. (H.R.E.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 25. 1957, Aug. 13.Monterey, Ca. E[lla] N. F[itch] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 26. 1957, Sept. 6.Stockton, Ca. Warmke & Woodward (L.E.W.) to John Inglis., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1957, Sept. 20.Stockton, Ca. Warmke & Woodward (L.E.W.) to William G. Phoenix., T.L.S.
    - 28. 1957, Sept. 24.Monterey, Ca. E[lla] N. F[itch] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 29. 1957, Sept. 29.Monterey, Ca. E[lla] N. F[itch] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 30. 1957, Sept. 30.Santa Cruz, Ca. Board of Supervisors, County of Santa Cruz (H.H.M.) to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1957, Oct. 20.Monterey, Ca. E[lla] N. F[itch] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 32. 1957, Oct. 29.Monterey, Ca. Ella [N] Fitch to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 33. 1957, Nov. 13.Redwood City, Ca. Mary Louise [Lyon] to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 34. 1957, Dec. 3.Davenport, Ca. W.W.S. to John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. re: legal matters - W.W.Steele vs. Inglis., T.L.S.
    - 35. 1957, Dec. 23.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.E.S.) to Stanley Steele re: bridge over Green Oak Creek., T.L.
    - 36. 1957, Dec. 23.Santa Cruz, Ca. Doc. F. to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 37. 1957, Dec. 24.Santa Cruz, Ca. County Bank of Santa Cruz (R.J.S.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 38. 1958, Jan. 13.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.E.S.) to C.B.S. re: bridge over Green Oak Creek., T.L.S.
    - 39. 1958, Jan. 29.Berkeley, Ca. Bancroft Library (E.G.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 40. 1958, Feb. 4.Schulenburg, Texas. O.H. Wolters to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 41. 1958, Feb. 13.Le Port, Texas. Capt. Jack McKeoren (?) to [C.]B.S., A.L.S.
    - 42. 1958, Feb. 14.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co., Inc. (S.L.T.) to Member., T.L.
    - 43. 1958, Feb. 27.Modesto, Ca. John Inglis Frozen Foods, Co. (E.B.**) to C.B.S. re: rent matters., T.L.S.
    - 44. 1958, Mar. 7.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co., Inc. (E.J.A.*) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 45. 1958, Mar. 10.Stockton, Ca. Warmke & Woodward (L.E.W.) to Eugene Boone re: legal matters - W.W.Steele vs. John Inglis Frozen Foods Co., T.L.S.
    - 46. 1958, Mar. 12.San Jacinto Monument, Texas. San Jacinto Museum of History Assc. (D.B.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 47. 1958, [Mar.] 13.Loma Mar. Cecil(?) Pearl Nelson to Friend [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 48. 1958, Mar. 13.Loma Mar. Cecil Nelson to Friend. [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 49. 1958, June 2.N.P. [Santa Cruz, Ca.]. Murphy & Adams to Severnson, Davis & Larson., T.L.
    - 50. 1958, June 3.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 51. 1958, June 9.S.F., Ca. Harold H. Alvarez to C.[B.S.], A.L.S.
    - 52. 1958, June 9.Stockton, Ca. Warmke & Woodward (L.E.W.) to Frank J. Murphy., T.L.S.
    - 53. 1958, June 9.Stockton, Ca. Warmke & Woodward (L.E.W.) to Eugene Boone., T.L.S.
    - 54. 1958, June 10.S.F., Ca. Severson, Davis & Larson (A.W.W.) to Murphy & Adams re: legal matters - John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. & sublease of Steele Ranch property., T.L.S.
    - 55. 1958, June 17.Honolulu, Hawaii. Bernice P. Bishop Museum (M.T.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 56. 1958, June 25.S.F., Ca. Wells Fargo Bank (I.W.H.) to F.W. Doyle., T.L.S.
    - 57. 1958, June 27.N.P. Unidentified to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 58. 1958, July 15.N.P. Pacific Guano Co. to W.[W.]S. re: legal matters., T.L.
    - 59. 1958, July 18.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co., Inc. (S.L.T.) to Member., T.L.
    - 60. 1958, July 23.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M. to C.B.S. re: Highway Dept. right-of-way., T.L.S.
    - 61. 1958, July 24.N.P. Pacific Guano Co. to William G. Phoenix re: legal matters., T.L.
    - 62. 1958, Sept. 16.S.F., Ca. Division of Highways (E.D.H. to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 63. 1958, Sept. 17.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M. to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 64. 1958, Oct. 2.S.F., Ca. Theresa Meikle to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 65. 1958, Oct. 23.S.F., Ca. Wells Fargo Bank (I.S.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 66. 1958, Oct. 28.Same as # 65.
    - 67. 1958, Oct. 29.N.P. _____ (?) to C.[B.]S. re: financial matters., A.L.S.
    - 68. 1958, Nov. 13.San Jose, Ca. Nat'l. Farm Loan Assc. (E.W.K.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 69. 1959, Jan. 6.Fresno, Ca. Carolin(?) Randall to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 70. 1959, Feb. 19.Monterey, Ca. Pauline McCleary to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 71. 1959, April 2.Same as # 70.
    - 72. 1959, April 28.N.P. Pauline McCleary to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 73. 1959, May 26.Monterey, Ca. Rollo Peters to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 74. 1959, May 29.Fresno, Ca. Division of Housing (S.G.L.) to [C.B.]S. re: employee housing., T.L.S.
    - 75. 1959, June 8.Coastways Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. Henry H. Bradley to Ralph Kenworthy re: Waddell water use., T.L.
    - 76. 1959, June 9.Coastways Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. Mary De F. Atkins to Mrs. Charles A. McLean Jr. re: Waddell water use., T.L.
    - 77. 1959, June 10.Santa Cruz, Ca. Emmet L. Rittenhouse to Murphy & Adams., T.L.S.
    - 78. 1959, June 11.Casa del Oso, Davenport, Ca. Hulda Hoover McLean to Mrs. David Atkins re: Waddell water use., T.L.
    - 79. Same as # 74.
    - 80. 1959, June 11.Santa Cruz, Ca. W.W.S. to John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. re: Waddell water use., T.L.
    - 81. 1959, June 12.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M. to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 82. 1959, June 18.[Santa Cruz, Ca.]. Murphy & Adams to Emmet L. Rittenhouse., T.L.
    - 83. 1959, June 19.Santa Cruz, Ca. John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. to W.W.S., T.L.
    - 84. 1959, June 21.San Juan Bautista, Ca. Division of Beaches & Parks (A.R.I.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 85. 1959, July 2.Monterey, Ca. Ella N. F[itch] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 86. 1959, Sept. 8.Monterey, Ca. E[lla] N. F[itch] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 87. 1959, Sept. 12.S.F., Ca. Marques E. Reitzel to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 88. 1959, Sept. 29.Monterey, Ca. Division of Beaches & Parks (A.K.*) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 89. 1959, Oct. 21.Monterey, Ca. Division of Beaches & Parks (J.T.C.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 90. 1959, Nov. 19.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M. to Ralph Kenworthy re: lease matters - Green Oak Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 91. 1959, Nov. 6.Green Oak Ranch, Pescadero, Ca. C.B.S. to Lorraine Dickey, tax collector., A.L.S.
    - 92. 1959, Nov. 19.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M. to John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. re: lease - Green Oaks Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 93. 1959, Nov. 20.N.P. H[ank] Sciaroni to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 94. 1959, Dec. 29.Santa Cruz, Ca. Duncan A. Holbert, M.D. to Mrs. W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - 1. 1960, Jan. 11.S.F., Ca. Duck Hunters Assc. of Calif. (C.F.W.) to Thomas H. Kuchel. Letter forwarded by W.P. Caubu for Duck Hunters Assc. of Calif., T.L.
    - 2. 1960, Jan. 30.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Ralph Kenworthy re: lease - Green Oaks Ranch., T.L.
    - 3. 1960, Feb. 4.[Santa Cruz, Ca.]. Murphy & Adams to William G. Phoenix re: lease - Green Oaks Ranch., T.L.
    - 4. 1960, Feb. 8.Half Moon Bay, Ca. Univ. of Calif. Agric. Extension Service (R.H.S.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 5. 1960, Feb. 10.Redwood City, Ca. William G. Phoenix to Leon E. Warmke re: lease - Green Oaks Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1960, Feb. 15.Modesto, Ca. John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. (R.K.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1960, Mar. 24.Half Moon Bay, Ca. Soil Conservation District (F.E.C.) to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 8. 1960, Mar. 30.Berkeley, Ca. Berkeley Camera Club (L.R.P.) to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 9. 1960, April 1.Fresno, Ca. Division of Housing (S.G.L.) to [C.B.]S. re: employee housing improvement., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1960, April 7.N.P. Dorothy H. to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 11. 1960, April 18.N.P. Virginia Snow to C.[B.S.]., A.L.
    - 12. 1960, April 26.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to William R. Bascom., T.L.
    - 13. 1960, April 30.Santa Cruz, Ca. R.B. Bernard to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 14. 1960, May 3.Berkeley, Ca. Museum of Anthropology, Univ. of Berkeley (W.B.) to Donald O. May., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1960, May 3.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy (?) to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 16. 1960, May 5.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 17. 1960, May 5.N.P. George L. Harding to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 18. 1960, May 9.Fresno, Ca. Division of Housing (S.G.L.) to [C.B.]S. re: employee housing., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1960, May 19.Colma, Ca. Bridgie E. Callan to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 20. 1960, May 23.Santa Cruz, Ca. Edevia (?) and Matilda Duval to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 21. 1960, May 24.Same as # 18.
    - 22. 1960, May 26.Houston, Texas. Unknown to C.[B.S.]., T.L.
    - 23. 1960, May 30.San Mateo, Ca. Calif. Garden Clubs, Inc. (L.B.K.) to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 24. 1960, June 20.N.P. J.M. to Steele., A.N.S.
    - 25. 1960, June 23.Redwood City, Ca. San Mateo County Planning Commission (B.M.) to Murphy & Adams re: permit to quarry sand from Annyo [Ao] Nuevo Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1960, June 27.Redwood City, Ca. San Mateo County Planning Commission (B.M.) to Murphy & Adams re: quarry permit., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1960, July 12.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy(?) to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 28. 1960, July 28.Santa Cruz, Ca. R.B. Bernard to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 29. 1960, Aug. 1.N.P. Alice Pittinger to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 30. 1960, Aug. 22.Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Farm Bureau Fed. (L.A.R.) to Farm Bureau Member., T.L.S.
    - 31. 1960, Sept. 4.N.P. Mother to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 32. 1960, Sept. 18.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy [H. Huggins] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 33. 1960, Sept. 29.Carmel, Ca. Eben Whittlesey to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 34. 1960, Oct. 2.N.P. Janie & Tom Dunlap to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 35. 1960, Oct. 18.N.P. Irene Simpson to Ellis Lucia., T.L.
    - 36. 1960, Oct. 31.[Santa Cruz, Ca.]. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to William G. Phoenix., T.L.
    - 37. 1960, Nov. 7.Santa Cruz, Ca. _____(?) Baldwin to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 38. 1960, Nov. 15.Redwood City, Ca. William G. Phoenix to Murphy & Adams re: lease - Green Oaks Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 39. 1960, Nov. 28.Modesto, Ca. John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. (R.K.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 40. 1960, Dec. 2.[Santa Cruz, Ca.]. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to William G. Phoenix., T.L.
    - 41. 1960, Dec. 13.Redwood City, Ca. William G. Phoenix to Murphy & Adams re: lease - Green Oaks Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 42. 1960, Dec. 14.Watsonville, Ca. Pajaro Valley Bank (O.B.L.) to Stockholders., T.L.S.
    - 43. 1960, Dec. 19.Watsonville, Ca. Pajaro Valley Bank (O,B.L.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 44. 1960, Dec. 31.N.P. Modred to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - 1. 1961, Jan. 9.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co., Inc. (E.J.A.*) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S. (Folder 29)
    - 2. 1961, Jan. 15.Santa Cruz, Ca. Santa Cruz Land & Cattle Co., Inc. (E.B.) to Member., T.L.
    - 3. 1961, Feb. 1.S.F., Ca. Forden Athearn, attorney, to Donald May., T.L.S.
    - 4. 1961, Feb. 7.Felton, Ca. Alice Pittinger to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 5. 1961, Feb. 9.Salinas, Ca. Paul Caswell to Wm. Jeffrey., T.L.S.
    - 6. 1961, Feb. 10.Salinas, Ca. W.W.S. & B.M.S. to John Inglis Frozen Foods, Co. re: taxes., T.L.
    - 7. 1961, Feb. 10.Same as # 6.
    - 8. 1961, Feb. 10.S.F., Ca. Harold H. Alvarez, D.D.S. to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 9. 1961, Feb. 13.N.P. Donald May to Forden Athearn re: property of C.B.S., T.L.
    - 10. 1961, Feb. 16.Modesto, Ca. John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. (R.K.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1961, Feb. 21.Stockton, Ca. [Mrs. Gerald D.] Kennedy to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 12. 1961, Feb. 28.Modesto, Ca. John Inglis Frozen Foods Co. (R.K.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 13. 1961, Mar. 7.Fresno, Ca. Division of Housing (S.G.L.) to Acme Farms re: employee housing., T.L.
    - 14. 1961, Mar. 15.S.F., Ca. Wells Fargo Bank to Stock-holders., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1961, April 3.Redwood, City, Ca. Lorraine A. Dickey, tax collector, to [C.B.]S., T.L.
    - 16. 196, April 11.[Santa Cruz, Ca.]. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to William G. Phoenix re: lease - Green Oaks Ranch., T.L.
    - 17. 1961, April 19.Salinas, Ca. Fed. Land Bank Assc. of Salinas (D.K.M.) to Donald O. May., T.L.S.
    - 18. 1961, April 21.Redwood City, Ca. Redwood City Tribune (M.M.G.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1961, April 28.N.P. C.B.S. to Baikie & Alcantara., T.L.
    - 20. 1961, May 2.Same as # 13.
    - 21. 1961, May 15.Santa Cruz, Ca. County Bank of Santa Cruz (W.S.L.) to Court Reporter, Santa Cruz., T.L.S.
    - 22. 1961, May 22.Fresno, Ca. Division of Housing (S.G.L.) to Acme Farms., T.L.
    - 23. 1961, May 25.N.P. Unidentified to [C.B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 24. 1961, June 4.S.F., Ca. Rue Clifford to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 25. 1961, June 12.San Mateo, Ca. San Mateo County Historical Assc. (F.M.S.) to Mrs. W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1961, June 21.N.P. Mrs. Fabian Bettencourt to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 27. 1961, June 25.San Mateo, Ca. Rudolp Lapp to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 28. 1961, July 21.Redwood City, Ca. Redwood City Tribune (M.[M.]G.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 29. 1961, July 22.N.P. M. to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 30. 1961, July 26.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 31. 1961, Aug. 2.Menlo Park, Ca. Fox & Carskadon Inc. (H.L.) to Murphy & Adams., T.L.S.
    - 32. 1961, Sept. 8.El Cerrito, Ca. Catherine Kerr to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 33. 1961, Sept. 8.El Cerrito, Ca. Mrs. Clark Kerr to Murphy & Adams re: Pigeon Point property., T.L.S.
    - 34. 1961, Sept. 22.Santa Cruz, Ca. Murphy & Adams (D.O.M.) to Mrs. Clark Kerr re: Pigeon Point property., T.L.
    - 35. 1961, Sept. 29.Santa Cruz, Ca. Chuck [McLean] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 36. 1961, Oct. 13.Half Moon Bay, Ca. University of Calif. Agricultural Extension Service (R.H.S.)
    - 37. 1961, Oct. 16.N.P. Unknown to Mrs. Atkins re: county general plan., T.L.
    - 38. 1961, Oct. 17.N.P. Louise to C[B.S.], T.L.S.
    - 39. 1961, Oct. 23.S.F., Ca. John Howell Books (W.R.H.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.